[Music]
Nita Desai Traffic DCP West Ahmedabad
City The special purpose of the traffic awareness
program organized by ICICI Lombard today was
that
school children should get
an understanding of wearing helmets on two-wheelers from now on.
Their parents have also been
kept with them and helmets have also been
distributed to them. Therefore, a message has been given that children and
parents should wear helmets whenever they go on two-wheelers.
If this
understanding is given to children from now on, then surely
whenever their parents
drive two-wheelers at home, the children themselves will
let them wear helmets that you should drive two-wheelers only after wearing a helmet.
This is a traffic sense that needs to be
developed from now on. This is a
really good effort from ICICI Lombard
and our Ahmedabad City Traffic also
appreciates their efforts.
Ahmedabad City Traffic and
ICICI Lombard
helped in this program in distributing helmets and traffic.  Thanks to the
awareness program organized in this program, the
sense of traffic will really develop in children. Jai Hind Jai Bharat